lazaruslabs.com 2019-04-14

# Privacy Policy – LazarusLabs.com

Lazarus Labs recognizes your need for protection of your privacy and for responsible management of personally identifiable information that you share with us, including information by which you can be identified. We have established this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our respect for, and commitment to, protecting your privacy.

When you register with Lazarus Labs we obtain certain information about you, including your internet address. Our company tracks internet addresses of domains from which users visit us and utilizes this information to help identify customers and their purchases as well as to help administer our website.

**What information we collect:**

**We may collect the following information:**

  * First name, last name, and title
  * Contact information such as telephone number & email address
  * Demographic information such as address, IP address & approximate geographic area

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better user experience when visiting our site, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Placing, processing, fulfilling, and shipping your order(s)
  * Internal record keeping
  * Analyze demographic and geographical location data via Google Analytics using cookies
  * Provide you with website sharing services and social network connectors
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products & special offers
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes
  * We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests
  * Serve you ads & reminders for our own products via display advertising, social media networks such as Facebook, Instagram, and Twitter, and email

**Email marketing services**

From time to time, we may contact you regarding offers and updates on our products and services. These emails may be personalized to contain your name for promotional reasons.

You may follow the ' **Unsubscribe** ' link in the footer of marketing emails to unsubscribe from them directly at any time.

**How you can move or block cookie use at any time**

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website and prevent you from placing an order.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic security software and procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added, and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better customer experience, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**AdRoll**

Lazarus Labs works with **[AdRoll retargeting](http://www.adroll.com/)** , who uses technology including web beacons and cookies to collect data about our website usage and to improve the effectiveness of our marketing. Data recorded through the use of this technology is aggregated and shared with us. No personally identifiable information about you is collected or shared by AdRoll with Lazarus Labs. You can opt-out of AdRoll and their partners by visiting this **[link](http://www.adroll.com/about/privacy)**.

As you browse the Lazarus Labs website, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in.  Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with LazarusLabs.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit **[this page to opt out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)** of AdRoll and their partners' targeted advertising.

**Advertising Partners**

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. While each of these advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their site, an updated and hyperlinked resource is maintained here: Our advertising partners include:

  * Google - **[Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy/)**
  * Facebook - **[Facebook Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php)**
  * AdRoll - **[AdRoll Privacy Policy](http://www.adroll.com/about/privacy)**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on LazarusLabs.com website and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site's third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site. The lazaruslabs.com website does not have access to or control these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**Newsletter**

As part of the registration process for our monthly e-newsletter, we collect personal information. We use that information for a couple of reasons: to tell you about stuff you’ve asked us to tell you about; to contact you if we need to obtain or provide additional information; to check our records are right and to check every now and then that you’re happy and satisfied. We don't rent or trade email lists with other organizations and businesses. Your information is safe and secure with us.

We use a third-party provider, www.klaviyo.com, to deliver our newsletter. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies to help us monitor and improve our e-newsletter. For more information, please see **_[Klaviyo’s privacy policy for more information.](https://www.klaviyo.com/privacy)_**

We also send emails from **[Gmail](https://policies.google.com/?hl=en)**, and from **[Shopify](https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy)**. Private messages on **[Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php) **may also be used to respond to customer inquiries only. You can review the privacy policies for each one of these platforms by clicking the hyperlinks attached. You can unsubscribe to general mailings at any time of the day or night by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our emails or by notifying us via our **_[Contact Us.](https://lazaruslabs.com/pages/contact-us)_**

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at customerservice@lazaruslabs.com.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this for this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.  If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to:

Lazarus Enterprises, Inc, 269 Market Pl Blvd, Cartersville, GA 30121 USA

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

**Contact information**

Lazarus Enterprises Inc, 269 Market Pl Blvd, Cartersville, GA 30121 USA. 

Email: customerservice@lazaruslabs.com

Telephone: [(888) 606-1002](https://www.google.com/search?ei=sz3bW_y1KMK7zwLdk5qgAg&q=Lazarus+Enterprises%2C+Inc+Cartersville+GA&oq=Lazarus+Enterprises%2C+Inc+Cartersville+GA&gs_l=psy-ab.3..33i160l2.2192.5204..5385...0.0..1.359.3260.0j3j6j4......0....1..gws-wiz.......0i22i30j33i299.nKiVP1FDfM0)

This privacy policy was updated on November 1, 2018.

**Right to Change Policy**

Lazarus Labs is constantly innovating and enhancing the products and services we provide. As such, we reserve the right to revise our Privacy Policy to match the products and services that we provide. To ensure that you are aware of any updates, we encourage you to check our Privacy Policy during every visit to the site or when you use our products and services.

Regardless of how this policy may change and evolve over time, Lazarus Labs will not collect or maintain your private and personal identifiable information without your consent. Should you submit personal information to Lazarus Labs, we will hold it in the strictest of confidence and will not sell, license or disclose said information to any third party without your prior consent.

Lazarus Labs, however, does reserve the right to disclose your personal information, if, required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of our company, it's employees, customers, or the public.

**Payment Processing**

Lazarus Labs is a Shopify e-commerce website. Payments captured through Shopify are safe and secure through PayPal. We do not share any payment or personal information with any data vendor, or partner. Our payment portal is secured and encrypted with SSL certificates and payment processing provided by PayPal. For more information, please review the privacy policies for both [Shopify](https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy) and [PayPal](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full).

**Children's privacy**

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. This Site is not intended or designed to attract children. Lazarus Labs does not knowingly or willingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of 18.

This Privacy Policy forms a legal agreement between you and Lazarus Labs. Your use of this website indicates your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. The Electronic Communications Privacy Act (ECPA) shall not apply to any communications with Lazarus Labs. Lazarus Labs reserves the right to make revisions to this agreement at any time without notice and will post changes and updates to the Privacy Policy by posting to this website.
